mingoville.com 2013-08-30

# Mingoville.com – بچے کے لیۓ انگریزی.

Mingoville is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Mingoville Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Mingoville website and the Mingoville application, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

### Collection of your Personal Information

For individual licenses Mingoville collects personally identifiable information such as your name and e-mail address. Mingoville also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your country and gender.

For school licenses Mingoville collects school’s identifiable information such as name, address and contact details. Mingoville also collects teacher’s personally identifiable information such as names and e-mail address. When registering students, a teacher is prompted to provide student’s personally identifiable information such as names, email address, gender and class name.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Mingoville. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Mingoville for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Mingoville Web site and the Mingoville application.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Mingoville public message boards (e.g. Blog etc.), this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Mingoville does not hold accountable in such instances.

Mingoville encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Mingoville so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Mingoville is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Mingoville and Mingoville family of Web sites.

### Use of your Personal Information

Mingoville collects and uses your personal information to operate the Mingoville Web site and the Mingoville application and deliver the services you have requested. Mingoville also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Mingoville and its affiliates. Mingoville may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Mingoville does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Mingoville may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Mingoville may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Mingoville, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Mingoville does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Mingoville keeps track of the Web sites and pages our users visit within the Mingoville website, in order to determine what Mingoville services are the most popular. Mingoville also keeps track of the learning area our users visit within the Mingoville application, in order to determine what Mingoville services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver most valuable services as well as customized content, and advertising to users within the Mingoville application.

Mingoville Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Mingoville, the site or the application; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Mingoville; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Mingoville, or the public.

### Use of Cookies

The Mingoville Web site uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Mingoville pages, or register with Mingoville site or services, a cookie helps Mingoville to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as postal addresses, telephones, and so on. When you return to the same Mingoville Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Mingoville features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Mingoville services or Web sites you visit.

### Security of your Personal Information

Mingoville secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Mingoville secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as passwords) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

### Changes to this Statement

Mingoville will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Mingoville encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Mingoville is protecting your information.

### Contact Information

Mingoville welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Mingoville has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Mingoville at[ info@mingoville.com](mailto:info@mingoville.com). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
